{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987106497","data":{"timestamp":" 946987106497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987106719","data":{"timestamp":" 946987106719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987107682","data":{"timestamp":" 946987107682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987108955","data":{"timestamp":" 946987108955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987111804","data":{"timestamp":" 946987111804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987112647","data":{"timestamp":" 946987112647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987112960","data":{"timestamp":" 946987112960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987114193","data":{"timestamp":" 946987114193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987117678","data":{"timestamp":" 946987117678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987118661","data":{"timestamp":" 946987118661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987118914","data":{"timestamp":" 946987118914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987119857","data":{"timestamp":" 946987119857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987122694","data":{"timestamp":" 946987122694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987123727","data":{"timestamp":" 946987123727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987124199","data":{"timestamp":" 946987124199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987128719","data":{"timestamp":" 946987128719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987128781","data":{"timestamp":" 946987128781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 26f36c21-10ef-42af-8f75-f7f6fe962c02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987142600","data":{"timestamp":" 946987142599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987151036","data":{"timestamp":" 946987151036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987152649","data":{"timestamp":" 946987152649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987155798","data":{"timestamp":" 946987155797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987157374","data":{"timestamp":" 946987157373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987162474","data":{"timestamp":" 946987162474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987164038","data":{"timestamp":" 946987164037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987168168","data":{"timestamp":" 946987168168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987169728","data":{"timestamp":" 946987169727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987174140","data":{"timestamp":" 946987174140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987175701","data":{"timestamp":" 946987175701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987180260","data":{"timestamp":" 946987180259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987181848","data":{"timestamp":" 946987181848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987189252","data":{"timestamp":" 946987189252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987190875","data":{"timestamp":" 946987190874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987194810","data":{"timestamp":" 946987194810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987196380","data":{"timestamp":" 946987196380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987199850","data":{"timestamp":" 946987199849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987201476","data":{"timestamp":" 946987201476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987205554","data":{"timestamp":" 946987205554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987207132","data":{"timestamp":" 946987207132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987211169","data":{"timestamp":" 946987211168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987213197","data":{"timestamp":" 946987213195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987213456","data":{"timestamp":" 946987213456"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" b4b7f8f0-c554-4437-839f-6f7308e7eb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987229942","data":{"timestamp":" 946987229941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987230173","data":{"timestamp":" 946987230172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987231147","data":{"timestamp":" 946987231146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987232437","data":{"timestamp":" 946987232436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987235403","data":{"timestamp":" 946987235402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987236255","data":{"timestamp":" 946987236254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987236579","data":{"timestamp":" 946987236578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987237811","data":{"timestamp":" 946987237811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987241338","data":{"timestamp":" 946987241338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987242334","data":{"timestamp":" 946987242334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987242599","data":{"timestamp":" 946987242598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987243554","data":{"timestamp":" 946987243553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987246461","data":{"timestamp":" 946987246461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987247508","data":{"timestamp":" 946987247508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987247991","data":{"timestamp":" 946987247990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987252545","data":{"timestamp":" 946987252544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987252620","data":{"timestamp":" 946987252620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" fccc6afd-732b-4d51-8dbd-874fa18ce033"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987262987","data":{"timestamp":" 946987262986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987263219","data":{"timestamp":" 946987263219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987264194","data":{"timestamp":" 946987264193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987265477","data":{"timestamp":" 946987265476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987268416","data":{"timestamp":" 946987268415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987269271","data":{"timestamp":" 946987269270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987269593","data":{"timestamp":" 946987269593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987270838","data":{"timestamp":" 946987270838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987274436","data":{"timestamp":" 946987274435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987275430","data":{"timestamp":" 946987275430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987275693","data":{"timestamp":" 946987275692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987276646","data":{"timestamp":" 946987276646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987279576","data":{"timestamp":" 946987279576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987280635","data":{"timestamp":" 946987280635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987281119","data":{"timestamp":" 946987281118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987285658","data":{"timestamp":" 946987285657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987285747","data":{"timestamp":" 946987285747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" e0329dd8-615d-4a51-ae93-b2d80d34e67e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987301596","data":{"timestamp":" 946987301596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukweli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKWELI"," userResponse":" UKWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987305684","data":{"timestamp":" 946987305683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukweli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKWELI"," userResponse":" UKWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987307272","data":{"timestamp":" 946987307272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maswali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987311632","data":{"timestamp":" 946987311632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maswali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987313241","data":{"timestamp":" 946987313241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tafadhali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987317450","data":{"timestamp":" 946987317450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tafadhali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987319063","data":{"timestamp":" 946987319062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kivuli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIVULI"," userResponse":" KIVULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987322063","data":{"timestamp":" 946987322062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kivuli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIVULI"," userResponse":" KIVULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987323676","data":{"timestamp":" 946987323675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAROLI"," userResponse":" TAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987326680","data":{"timestamp":" 946987326680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAROLI"," userResponse":" TAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987328290","data":{"timestamp":" 946987328289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miwili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWILI"," userResponse":" MIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987338544","data":{"timestamp":" 946987338543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miwili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987340152","data":{"timestamp":" 946987340151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akadeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKADELI"," userResponse":" AKADELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987343414","data":{"timestamp":" 946987343414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akadeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKADELI"," userResponse":" AKADELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987345034","data":{"timestamp":" 946987345033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987353959","data":{"timestamp":" 946987353958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987355537","data":{"timestamp":" 946987355536"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umbali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" UMBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987359978","data":{"timestamp":" 946987359978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umbali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987361577","data":{"timestamp":" 946987361577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987364431","data":{"timestamp":" 946987364431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987366458","data":{"timestamp":" 946987366457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987366573","data":{"timestamp":" 946987366573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987416629","data":{"timestamp":" 946987416629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987431978","data":{"timestamp":" 946987431978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" c27621cb-c1ad-4999-94ab-c57ab1281ef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987441819","data":{"timestamp":" 946987441819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987442042","data":{"timestamp":" 946987442042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987443006","data":{"timestamp":" 946987443006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987444292","data":{"timestamp":" 946987444291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987447252","data":{"timestamp":" 946987447251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987448108","data":{"timestamp":" 946987448107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987448427","data":{"timestamp":" 946987448426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987449670","data":{"timestamp":" 946987449669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987453246","data":{"timestamp":" 946987453246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987454236","data":{"timestamp":" 946987454235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987454497","data":{"timestamp":" 946987454497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987455452","data":{"timestamp":" 946987455451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987458411","data":{"timestamp":" 946987458411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987459455","data":{"timestamp":" 946987459455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987459934","data":{"timestamp":" 946987459934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987464498","data":{"timestamp":" 946987464497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987464589","data":{"timestamp":" 946987464589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 083023e7-e34d-4e8b-8f3d-77e8cbb5c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987502376","data":{"timestamp":" 946987502376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 7c834cc4-b3c3-4cb5-ade1-11e3e1bdc9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" Q"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987505038","data":{"timestamp":" 946987505038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 7c834cc4-b3c3-4cb5-ade1-11e3e1bdc9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987522904","data":{"timestamp":" 946987522904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 7c834cc4-b3c3-4cb5-ade1-11e3e1bdc9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987528958","data":{"timestamp":" 946987528958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 7c834cc4-b3c3-4cb5-ade1-11e3e1bdc9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987530595","data":{"timestamp":" 946987530595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 7c834cc4-b3c3-4cb5-ade1-11e3e1bdc9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987544656","data":{"timestamp":" 946987544656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 7c834cc4-b3c3-4cb5-ade1-11e3e1bdc9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987552251","data":{"timestamp":" 946987552251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 7c834cc4-b3c3-4cb5-ade1-11e3e1bdc9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987557427","data":{"timestamp":" 946987557427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 7c834cc4-b3c3-4cb5-ade1-11e3e1bdc9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987565432","data":{"timestamp":" 946987565432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 7c834cc4-b3c3-4cb5-ade1-11e3e1bdc9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.li.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987575429","data":{"timestamp":" 946987575429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 7c834cc4-b3c3-4cb5-ade1-11e3e1bdc9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987622975","data":{"timestamp":" 946987622974"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 7c834cc4-b3c3-4cb5-ade1-11e3e1bdc9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.li.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write___li"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987636582","data":{"timestamp":" 946987636582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukweli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKWELI"," userResponse":" UKWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987640171","data":{"timestamp":" 946987640170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukweli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKWELI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987641730","data":{"timestamp":" 946987641729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maswali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987645611","data":{"timestamp":" 946987645611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maswali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987647164","data":{"timestamp":" 946987647164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tafadhali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987651344","data":{"timestamp":" 946987651344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tafadhali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987652924","data":{"timestamp":" 946987652924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kivuli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIVULI"," userResponse":" KIVULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987656612","data":{"timestamp":" 946987656612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kivuli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIVULI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987658168","data":{"timestamp":" 946987658168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAROLI"," userResponse":" TAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987661815","data":{"timestamp":" 946987661815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987663392","data":{"timestamp":" 946987663392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miwili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWILI"," userResponse":" MIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987668104","data":{"timestamp":" 946987668104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miwili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987669675","data":{"timestamp":" 946987669674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akadeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKADELI"," userResponse":" AKADELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987672615","data":{"timestamp":" 946987672615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akadeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKADELI"," userResponse":" AKADELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987674172","data":{"timestamp":" 946987674171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987693802","data":{"timestamp":" 946987693802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987695411","data":{"timestamp":" 946987695411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umbali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" UMBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987699833","data":{"timestamp":" 946987699833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umbali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987701417","data":{"timestamp":" 946987701417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987704340","data":{"timestamp":" 946987704340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" START_OVAROLI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987706936","data":{"timestamp":" 946987706936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.li.rand.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987708963","data":{"timestamp":" 946987708962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987709115","data":{"timestamp":" 946987709115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 9b795e23-9bdd-4731-84b7-9d65e5709fbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.li.rand.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987720437","data":{"timestamp":" 946987720436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987720669","data":{"timestamp":" 946987720668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987721641","data":{"timestamp":" 946987721640"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987722924","data":{"timestamp":" 946987722923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987725895","data":{"timestamp":" 946987725894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987726756","data":{"timestamp":" 946987726755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987727076","data":{"timestamp":" 946987727076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987728325","data":{"timestamp":" 946987728323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987731920","data":{"timestamp":" 946987731920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987732912","data":{"timestamp":" 946987732912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987733172","data":{"timestamp":" 946987733172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987734126","data":{"timestamp":" 946987734125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987737048","data":{"timestamp":" 946987737048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987738094","data":{"timestamp":" 946987738093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987738574","data":{"timestamp":" 946987738573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987743137","data":{"timestamp":" 946987743135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987743237","data":{"timestamp":" 946987743237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 5c5ef872-2755-403e-b959-de5d3d14cdee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987766156","data":{"timestamp":" 946987766156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wali_kima-wali-hana"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wali"," userResponse":" wali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987777984","data":{"timestamp":" 946987777984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hali_hali-taya-moyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hali"," userResponse":" hali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987792360","data":{"timestamp":" 946987792360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wali_koko-wali-pole"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wali"," userResponse":" wali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987802571","data":{"timestamp":" 946987802571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kali_kali-wazi-yote"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" kali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987819658","data":{"timestamp":" 946987819658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wali_wali-boga-jiwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wali"," userResponse":" wali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987833383","data":{"timestamp":" 946987833383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mali_mali-bila-hapa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mali"," userResponse":" mali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987843186","data":{"timestamp":" 946987843186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goli_titi-tani-goli"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goli"," userResponse":" titi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987853997","data":{"timestamp":" 946987853995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goli_titi-tani-goli"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goli"," userResponse":" goli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987872824","data":{"timestamp":" 946987872823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wali_goti-wali-hata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wali"," userResponse":" wali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987886373","data":{"timestamp":" 946987886373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pili_pili-yale-hapa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pili"," userResponse":" pili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987900484","data":{"timestamp":" 946987900484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bali_honi-wapi-bali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bali"," userResponse":" bali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987906242","data":{"timestamp":" 946987906241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 73451069-cf4d-4094-bd91-b4db2b8f09f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_bali_honi-wapi-bali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987924794","data":{"timestamp":" 946987924794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kali_kali-wazi-yote"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" kali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987936228","data":{"timestamp":" 946987936228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_goli_titi-tani-goli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goli"," userResponse":" goli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987945520","data":{"timestamp":" 946987945520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bali_honi-wapi-bali"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bali"," userResponse":" bali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987956385","data":{"timestamp":" 946987956385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hali_hali-taya-moyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hali"," userResponse":" hali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987965489","data":{"timestamp":" 946987965489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wali_koko-wali-pole"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wali"," userResponse":" koko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987974217","data":{"timestamp":" 946987974217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wali_koko-wali-pole"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wali"," userResponse":" wali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987983605","data":{"timestamp":" 946987983605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wali_kima-wali-hana"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wali"," userResponse":" wali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988000903","data":{"timestamp":" 946988000903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wali_goti-wali-hata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wali"," userResponse":" wali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988011252","data":{"timestamp":" 946988011252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pili_pili-yale-hapa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pili"," userResponse":" pili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988023067","data":{"timestamp":" 946988023067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mali_mali-bila-hapa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mali"," userResponse":" mali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988035091","data":{"timestamp":" 946988035091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wali_wali-boga-jiwe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wali"," userResponse":" wali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.li.noShow.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988040829","data":{"timestamp":" 946988040829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 267b07e4-2873-4c9b-9d74-c317ce8c8956"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.li.noShow.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_wali_wali-boga-jiwe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988055329","data":{"timestamp":" 946988055329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 0af9302c-8ba5-43fa-aa4e-d66257392d21"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988060314","data":{"timestamp":" 946988060314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 0af9302c-8ba5-43fa-aa4e-d66257392d21"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988073592","data":{"timestamp":" 946988073592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 0af9302c-8ba5-43fa-aa4e-d66257392d21"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988084391","data":{"timestamp":" 946988084391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 0af9302c-8ba5-43fa-aa4e-d66257392d21"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988092232","data":{"timestamp":" 946988092232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 0af9302c-8ba5-43fa-aa4e-d66257392d21"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-2-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988101292","data":{"timestamp":" 946988101292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 0af9302c-8ba5-43fa-aa4e-d66257392d21"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988113343","data":{"timestamp":" 946988113343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 0af9302c-8ba5-43fa-aa4e-d66257392d21"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988115196","data":{"timestamp":" 946988115196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 0af9302c-8ba5-43fa-aa4e-d66257392d21"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988130742","data":{"timestamp":" 946988130742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 704d2ab0-e045-425a-9e95-d54f9c05deb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_dudu-mama-kuna"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988142097","data":{"timestamp":" 946988142097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 704d2ab0-e045-425a-9e95-d54f9c05deb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kama_sasa-kama-jike"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kama"," userResponse":" kama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988155388","data":{"timestamp":" 946988155388"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 704d2ab0-e045-425a-9e95-d54f9c05deb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_boma_boma-koti-yuko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" boma"," userResponse":" boma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988165145","data":{"timestamp":" 946988165145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 704d2ab0-e045-425a-9e95-d54f9c05deb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lima_hana-ubao-lima"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lima"," userResponse":" lima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988176048","data":{"timestamp":" 946988176048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 704d2ab0-e045-425a-9e95-d54f9c05deb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hema_hema-niwe-tani"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hema"," userResponse":" hema"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988187260","data":{"timestamp":" 946988187260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 704d2ab0-e045-425a-9e95-d54f9c05deb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_boma_dawa-boma-sote"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" boma"," userResponse":" boma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988187508","data":{"timestamp":" 946988187508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_145809"," gameId":" 704d2ab0-e045-425a-9e95-d54f9c05deb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_boma_dawa-boma-sote"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}